<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Des Moines Real Estate Podcast with Timothy Schutte</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from EXIT Realty Capital City - your professional Des Moines Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Timothy Schutte</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-05-14 11:03:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Timothy Schutte</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Des Moines, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>timothy@solddesmoines.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Timothy Schutte</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Timothy Schutte</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Des Moines, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Des Moines Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from EXIT Realty Capital City - your professional Des Moines Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Does Brandy Underberg Do for Our Team?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-does-brandy-underbug-do-for-our-team.html</link>
        
          <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        <author>Timothy Schutte</author>
        <pubDate>2020-05-04 15:46:09 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Timothy+Schutte/What+Does+Brandy+Underbug+Do+for+Our+Team_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Brandy Underberg has progressed more in this last year than she ever imagined she could at any other brokerage.

Brandy Underberg has been with our team as a Realtor for about six months. We’re proud to have her aboard, and today she joins me for a quick interview. 

What Brandy likes most about working here is the team environment. Everyone in our office is willing to build each other up and help each other out. If anyone has questions or ideas they’d like to bounce off someone else, there’s always someone available. 

Our onboarding process was different than Brandy’s previous experiences in that she learned many different prospecting techniques and progressive time blocking information. She also learned a lot of good things about statistics, the best times to call people, and how often to call them. 

“Our team’s culture has been progressive and ever-changing, and Brandy’s experience with that culture has been nothing but positive.”

This has greatly benefited her career because all of this training and prospecting has provided her with numerous leads. In just six months, she’s already handled several transactions, and she says she’s progressed more in this last year than she ever imagined she could at any other brokerage. 

“There are just the right things in place here that will help you move forward and make you a good agent,” she says. 

Speaking for myself, I think our team’s culture has been progressive and ever-changing, and Brandy’s experience with that culture has been nothing but positive. 

“I love the culture. I feel like we have the most relaxed and encouraging environment here. I don’t feel that it’s necessarily the most competitive, and that’s good for me. I’m a self-competitive person. I feel more like it’s a cooperative environment—that we all just kind of work together and help each other out, and we all want to move to the next level together.” 

We look forward to the many years to come with Brandy on our team. As always, if you have any questions or real estate needs, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’re here to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Timothy+Schutte/What+Does+Brandy+Underbug+Do+for+Our+Team_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Timothy+Schutte/What+Does+Brandy+Underbug+Do+for+Our+Team_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Brandy Underberg has progressed more in this last year than she ever imagined she could at any other brokerage.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Timothy Schutte</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Brandy Underberg has progressed more in this last year than she ever imagined she could at any other brokerage.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Des Moines, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Timothy Schutte</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Timothy Schutte</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from EXIT Realty Capital City - your professional Des Moines Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
